explain this experiment i'm going to use
a plasma ball to excite
the bashar sda the plasma ball
is 21 inches
away from the base or the the edge base
of the
tetrahedron the
outer surface of the tetrahedron
is the outer wall of the capacitor the
inner wall is connected to the top of
the coil
and the bottom of the coil comes out the
green wire so
it's a coil
i'm sorry it's a capacitor as the
antenna
and coil underneath that going
to the green wire come in coming into my
germanium ac to dc converter
and then there'll be a load across
there a very various homage
and then we'll read out the voltage here
and then we can convert to power
no i'm going to use uh
these various loads 1k
2k 250k 470k 850k
and 2 mega ohm these are the values
as you read them on the resistors
not not the values in terms of a
measured homage
so this would be plus or minus uh 10 to
20 percent
because these parts are not exact but um
anyway this will give us a rough idea
now we'd like to know whether the power
that we get
from that distance is linear
or whether um with less of a resistance
the power reception increases i also
wanted to make a
special note that you you want to
connect
the negative side of this converter
to ground so i have it connected to
ground
which is basically the uh
the plumbing of my house
um so we'll fire this thing up oh the
other thing is you want to keep this
circuit
uh on the opposite side of the plasma
ball you want the plasma ball to be the
closest thing to the tetrahedron
with nobody in between here if you put
your hand in here
or if you're sitting in here the energy
transfer
fur is way better or if you had anything
metallic in here
i'm using 21 inches because that seems
to be
sort of that fuzzy area between the near
field and the far field
okay turning this on turning
this on
what i should do is have it it had
the caps had a charge on it so i'm going
to short out the caps
put the load on there again let it grow
back
now those uh beeps coming to the meter
are
interesting those are like um
a little spikes or little arcs coming in
and
the meter is warning over voltage but
it's so rapid that it's
not a big deal
okay i'm going to say 3.62
okay the caps are shorted out again
starting from zero
putting the 220 ohm
on there
we have a much higher voltage
so
here okay we have the 59 loads
and
okay starting from the shorter cap again
now we're gonna do the 470k
this is approaching
do
okay
we overshot it
a little bit uh so the tetrahedron is a
capacitor
there's an outer surface an inner
surface the inner surface is top
touching the top of the coil the bottom
of the coil is our antenna lead
so nothing here is grounded
it is purely acting as an antenna coming
into the ac to dc converter
and then we're measuring so
let me write down that final number and
crunch
the results
um
you